So, to calculate the lifetime value,
计算客户生命周期价值
let's use this formula.
要用到这个公式
We're going to go ahead and break each piece up,
会把公式先拆解一下
so that we can see how to calculate each of these components of the formula,
看看如何计算公式中的每一个部分
and we're going to use the week r example again.
再次用到 WeCart 的例子
Let's assume a typical week our customer orders groceries once a week,
假设 WeCart 客户平均一周会下单购买一次
for say $70 per order.
假设每订单 70 美元
So, our purchase cycle we can make it to be one week,
那么 购买周期为一星期
total sales revenue per cycle would be the $70 we
每周期总销售收入为 70 美元
expect to earn from the customer during this purchase cycle,
这是我们预期在购买周期内从每个客户赚取的收入
to 70, and then the number of sales per
填入 70  然后是购买周期销售量
purchase cycle would be the number of times the customer buys during the purchase cycle,
即客户在购买周期内的购买次数
which would be one order per week.
设为每星期一次订单
So, one order per customer cycle, which is one.
那么 每购买周期一次订单 填入 1
Now, let's go ahead and calculate the other pieces of the formula.
接下来计算公式的其他部分
To calculate the other two pieces of the formula,
对于公式的另外两个部分
you need to take into account cost per acquisition as well as average sales revenue.
需要考虑每次获取成本以及平均销售收入
So, let's walk through these.
让我们一起来看看这两个方面
So, the cost per acquisition is the CPR that we've calculated before.
每次获取成本也就是 CPA 我们之前解释过如何计算
So, let's assume this to be $25.
假设这个值为 25 美元
So, it takes about $25 of sales and marketing costs to get a need.
需要花费 25 美元的营销销售成本来获取一位潜在客户
The expected retention time is the amount of time
预期保留客户时间是指预期保留客户多久时间
which is measured in purchase cycles that you expect to retain the customer.
即 客户会在我们公司持续消费多久
I think we can aim a customer to stay with our business for, say seven years,
以购买周期为单位 假设为七年
when she say, think of our own experience as a grocery buyer and online shopper.
回想一下我们自己的网购经验
So, this would be seven years,
假设七年相对较为合理 对吧
but since we need this in the purchase cycles as that is our unit.
不过 由于是以购买周期为单位
So, we're going to go seven years times 52.
我们要把七年乘以 52
So, that's how I got this.
得出这个数字
So, this would be seven times 52 weeks per year,
算一下 — 7 年乘以每年 52 星期
so that gives us 364 weeks across seven years.
得出七年有 364 个星期
Average sales revenue is the average revenue we
平均销售收入是指
receive from the customer per transaction during the cycle.
购买周期内每次交易从客户赚取的平均收入
We calculate this above.
上面已经计算了
This is $70 per cycle,
每购买周期 70 美元
so that's 70 here,
填入 70
and then profit margin per customer.
接下来是客户利润
The way to calculate this is average sale,
计算方式是
which is $70 minus the average cost of sales.
平均销售额 70 美元 - 平均销售成本
So, this would be where you can plug in the cost per acquisition,
也就是 每次获取成本
so over the average sales.
分母是平均销售额
So, this would be this minus this over 70.
这个值减去另一个值之差 再除以 70
Okay. So, that's $0.64 on a dollar.
也就是说 平均一美元收入 可得到 0.64 美元利润
That's the profit margin per customer.
这就是客户利润
Now, we're ready to plug all of that in into the lifetime value formula.
现在 我们要把所有数值用到客户生命周期价值的公式当中
So, we're ready to plug in the values for the lifetime value now.
开始把所有数值用到客户生命周期价值的公式当中
So, this is going to be our average sale,
把平均销售收入 70 美元…
which is 70 times number for peak sales,
…乘以每购买周期销售量 1…
which is one times expected retention time,
…乘以预期保留客户时间…
which is these number of weeks across seven years times the profit margin.
…也就是七年的这么多个星期 乘以利润率
So, 16,380 or the value that a customer would bring to a company.
得出的值 16,380 是一位客户能给公司带来的价值
So, now that you know that an average customer value is 16,380,
现在知道了平均客户价值是 16,380
the company should spend less than this to obtain a new paying customer.
那么 公司为获得新的付费客户所花的成本应该少于这个值
It is spending more than this,
如果花费的成本超过这个值
the company may be making losses in the long run.
公司就可能长期陷入亏损
One other thing, I have seen several equations for lifetime value.
此外 有几个不同的公式都可以计算客户生命周期价值
It is generally recommended to calculate lifetime value using a few different ways,
一般建议用多种方式来计算客户生命周期价值
so you can get a better estimate of your average lifetime value.
以便做出更准确的预估
We've provided a few links below for you to
可以点击以下几个链接
see what are the other ways to calculate lifetime value of a customer.
了解如何用其他方式计算客户生命周期价值